Turner Memorial AME Church 2017.071 2017.071
Stage
Turner Memorial AME Church
1919-2015
Stage
2017.071
30 Linear feet 69 manuscript and large flat file boxes For three-dimensional objects only.
Good
Content Description
69 boxes of materials related to Turner Memorial African Methodist Episcopal Church documenting its ministries, parishioners, and church history. Materials include photographs, programs, published and other printed materials.
Religion; African American churches; Digital materials; Ephemera; Turner Memorial African Methodist Episcopal (AME) Church
- Bible, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bible (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Bible, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Bible, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Constitution and bylaw booklet, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Lay Organization, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Lay Organization, 1983/1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Lay Organization, 1996/2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Lay Organization, 1919/2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Turner Laity, 1983/2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Lay Organization, 1967/2011 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- The Organizations of the Church, their officers, their purpose, their mambers (Box 4, Folder 8)
- The Organizations of the Church, their officers, their purpose, their mambers, 2004-06-05 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Lay Organization Members and Officers (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Pastor White's Father, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Rev. Henry Y. White, Appointed 4/2014 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Rev. Henry White, 1979/2006 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Rev. Pauline L. Thurston, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Pastor's Resume, 1982/1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Rev. I. A. Miller (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Rev. C. C. Ferguson (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Rev. William H. Lamar IV, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Darryl E. Walker, 2009-02-06 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Rev Walker Anniversary Program and a Letter from House of Represenatives, 2005-2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Rev Darryl Walker's Appointment 10/28/2000, 2005-11-13 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Turner Welcomes Pastor Walker Presiding Elder and Mrs. Manning to his Right, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Welcome Walker, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Dubutante Presentation 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Debutante Presentation 1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Debutante Presentation 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Debutante 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Debutante 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Debutante 1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Debutante Presentation 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Debutante 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Debutante Presentation 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Debutante Presentation 1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Debutante Presentation 1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Debutante Presentation 1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Debutante Presentation 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Debutante Presentation 1969 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Debutante Presentation 1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Debutante Presentation 1967 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Debutante Presentation 1966 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Debutante Presentation 1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Debutante Presentation 1964 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Debutante Programs, 2004/2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Debutante Presentation 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Debutante Presentation 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Debutante Presentation 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Debutante Presentation 1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Debutante Presentation 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Debs 1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Debutante Presentation 1983 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Debutante Presentation 1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Debutante Presentation 1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Debutante Presentation 1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Debutante Presentation 2008 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Debutante Presentation 2007 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Debutante Presentation 2006 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Debutante Presentation 2005 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Debutante Presentation 2004 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Debutante, 1964/2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Debutante Presentation, 1964/1965 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Debutante Presentation, 1980/1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Debutante, 1976/1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Debutante, 1968/1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Debutante, 1964/1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Debutante, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- loose photographs, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Mother's Club 25th Anniversary, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Mother's Day 1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Mother's Day 1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Mother's Day 1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Mother's Day 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Mother's Day 1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Mother's Day 1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Mother's Day 1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Mother's Day 1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Mother's Day 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- "1989" (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Mother's Day 1991 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Mother's Day 1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Mother's Day 1986 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Mother's Day 1969, 1984, 2003, 1969/2003 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Mother's Day 1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Mother's Day 1966 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Mother's Day Service Program 1956 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Church Activities, 2002/2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Womens History Month, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- "1987", 1987-01-05 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- I. A. Miller Circle theatre, Sunday may 18, 1997, 1997-05-18 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Fall Revival 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Installation Service 2005 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- 6th and I, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Good Friday, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- "2004" (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Adas Israel Congregation, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- "2003" (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Dewana Horton, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Willie M Dorsey, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- "1984" (Box 10, Folder 14)
- 64th Birthday 1983 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Men's Choir, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Family Day, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Founder's Day 1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- August 8 1972, 1972-08-20 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Choir Concert (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Christmas Expressions, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Woman's Day Committee (2000) (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Good Friday, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- "2009" (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Men's Fashion Show, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Tom Thumb Wedding, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- A Play 2001 Woman's Day (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Dinner Theater 1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Lucinda West's Birthday, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Church Organizations, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Turner's Church Organization Roster, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- A.B. Salters Club, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Boyscouts of America charter, 1965/1971 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Busy Bee Club, 1951/2002 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- College Ministry Day, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- The J. Dewitt Circle, 1951/1984 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Council of Presents South Africa Trip, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Council of Club Presidents, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- C.C. Ferguson Club, 1969/1984 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Summary of Interviews (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Father's Day, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Salvation Army Angel Tree Guide for Help, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Church Act, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Church Activity, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Bertha Mosby Birthday, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Picture CD 2007 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Revival, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Family and Friends Day, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Appreciation Luncheon, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Church School Christmas, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Tmame:Tutorial Program, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Church Activities, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Church Dedication, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Church Activities, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Harvest Revival Dec 17, 2001, 2001-12-17 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Church Activitiy, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Church Activities, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Prayer Breakfast, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Adas Israel 1997 MLK Day (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Church Activities, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Women's Shelter, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Senior Chior Concerts, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Amec Basketball Ministry, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- T.A.M.E. Times, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Adas Israel 1998 MLK Day (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Retired Honorees, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Church Calendar, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Honors Dinner 1978 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Mrs. Mosby Celebration (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Service Scrnery Hyattsville (Box 11, Folder 30)
- "1959" (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Adas Israel, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Lenten Season Celebration, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Church Activities (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Servicve, 6th and I Streets (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Name the Group (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Metropolitan A.M.E (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Adas Isreal at Turner (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Quilting Symbols (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Revival, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- 1985 Annual Calendar (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Retired Honoree's, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Loose Items, 1991/2004 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Church Activities (Box 11, Folder 44)
- 100th Celebration Joel Emmett McLeod, Sr., 2010-02-20 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Sr. Choir Programs, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Senior Choir Concert, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Programs, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Cristmas Program, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Christmas Program, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Christmas Program, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Festival Choir Members by voice and Alpha Sort, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Gospel Choir (2000) (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Extravaganza in Celebration of Project 99, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Sr. Choir Presents an Evening to Honor Mozella Preston, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Celestial Chorale Rooster, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- 1st Annual Christmas Celebration, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Gospel Choir Anniversary, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Everett Williams presented in concert by the Georgia club, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- gospel chorus, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Celebration of service banquet given by sr. choir, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Georgia Club Presents in Concert, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- 55th Anniversary of Sr. Usher Bd. #1, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Handel Messiah Presented by sr. choir, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Laymen Black History Program, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Sun. Service Bulletin, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Christmas Program Featuring the Young Peoples Choir, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Anne Guiles, Pianist in Concert, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Dennise Jackson in Recital, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- The Senior Chior the Messiah, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Performance by Sr. Choir (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Musical Program Honoring Mrs. Preston (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Sr. Choir Concert by: Frank Madison Reid Club (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Gospel Choir (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Nativity Scene Presented by the Combined 2nd and Mens Choir (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Treble Cleff Choir Members (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Senior Choir, 1951/2005 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Concerts, 1980/2002 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- 2nd Choir, 1951/1969 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Clubs, 1951/1994 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- A Taste of Turner, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Appreation Servive for Mrs. Preston (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Community Day, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Choirs (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Trustee Board, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Builders of Turner (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Missianory Sunday and Class Leaders, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- 44th Anniversary Programme, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Fiftieth Anniversary Programme, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- 64th Anniversary Programme, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- 75th Anniversary Programme, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- 80th Anniversary Programmes, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- 88th Anniversary Programmes, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- 90th Anniversary Programme, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- 94th Anniversary Programme, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- 100th Anniversary Programme, 2015 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Church Anniversary, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Founder's Day Gosple Choir (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Loose Items, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- "2013" (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Mother's Club 2011 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- 2011 Mother's Day (Box 14, Folder 3)
- 2010 Mother's Day (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Mother's Day Calendar, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Mother's Day, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Mother's Day, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Mother's Day, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Mother's Day, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Mother's Day Tribute, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Mother's Day, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Mother's Day, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- mother's Club (Box 14, Folder 13)
- AMEC Souvenir Journal, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- General Conf. Preparation, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- "2000" (Box 15, Folder 3)
- "1992" (Box 15, Folder 4)
- "1988" (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Highlights and Pictorial Review, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- 1976 - Assignment of Bishops Retirement of Bishops (Box 15, Folder 7)
- "2000" (Box 15, Folder 8)
- "1976" (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Quadrennial Report 1972-76, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- loose booklets, 1952/2008 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- 2012 AME Conference (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Obituaries A-F (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Obituaries G-L (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Obituaries M-R (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Obituaries S-Z (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Obituaries Unsorted (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Sons of Allen (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Call to Action and Men of Turner, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Men's Day Anniversary and Men's Club Anniversary Programs, 1942/2005 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Mens Day Procolamation, 1944/2002 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Mens Day Program, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Men's Day, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Turner's Men (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Mens Day, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Taste of Turner Mens Day (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Taste of Turner, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Mr. Spinor, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Annual Men's Day, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Favorite Scriptures, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Men's Day Committee, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Spirtual Fashion and Talent Show, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Father's Day Family Dinner, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Ledger, ca. 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Ledger, 1956/1957 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Binder, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Ledger, 1956/1957 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Ledger, 1946/1950 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Ledger, 1948/1953 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Ledger, 1949/1953 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Ledger, 1950/1955 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Ledger, 1951/1955 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Ledger, 1968/1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Ledger (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Ledger, 1979/1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Ledger, 1928/1930 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Notebook, 1963/1965 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Ledger, 1949/1951 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Ledger, 1925/1928 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Notebook, 1941/1944 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Notebook, 1951/1952 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Notebook, 1988/1996 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Notebook, 1963/1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Ledger, 1954/1958 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Ledger, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Ledger, 1962/1964 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- History A.M.E. Church, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- The Richard Allen Legacy (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Richard Allen, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- The Four Horsemen, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Heroes of African Methodistism (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Mclead Family (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Eva McCleod's Short Storm, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Photos of Joel McLeod, Sr. 100th Birthday Celebration, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Dr. Joseph McKinney (Box 30, Folder 4)
- 2nd Episcopal District Organization, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Laity 'The Voice', 2006 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Lay Organization, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- A.M.E. Lay, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Georgia Club First Trip, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Annual Women's Day, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Celestial Chorale Christmas, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Jr. Choirs Celestial Chorale, 1940/2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Lucille Ivy (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Treble Clef Choir, 1962/2002 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Men's Choir, 1969/1989 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Gospel Chorus, 1951/1984 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Celestral Chorale (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Senior Choir, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Sr. Choir Black History Celebration, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Melotones (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Treble Clef Choir (Box 31, Folder 11)
- 5th and P Choir (Box 31, Folder 12)
- loose Photographs (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Motown (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Liturgical Dance Ministry, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Turner Congragation, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Musicals/Pageants, 1955/1976 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Turner Mem Good Friday Program, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Church Activities, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- A Gape Dancers, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- 50th Ann I A Miller, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Virginia Club, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Georgia Club, 1998/2000 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Georgia Club, 1969/2002 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- South Carolina, 1951/2002 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Martin Luther King Calendar, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Martin Luther King, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Martin Luther (sixth and I), 2005 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- College Ministry, 1992/2003 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Children's Day, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Children's Day, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Loose Items, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Children's Day, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Scholarship Day, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Scholarship Comm, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Scholarship Day, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Scholarship Day, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Scholarship Day, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Scholarship Day, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Scholarship Day, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Scholarship Day, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Scholarship Day, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Scholarship Program, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Children's Day, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Scholarship Day, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Scholarship Day, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Children's Day, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Children's Day, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Children's Day, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Henry McNeal Turner Early Learning Center, 2004/2007 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Sunday School, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Youth Ministry Directory (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Church School Convention, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- "April 1959" (Box 36, Folder 4)
- "July 1960" (Box 36, Folder 5)
- "2008" (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Sunday School Class (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Christian Education (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Sunday School Easter Morning Program, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Sunday School (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Christian Ed Conf, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- "2007" (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Sun School (Easter Program), 2005 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Portrait Unveilling for Bedrice Williams, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- S S Easter Program, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Sunday School, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Church Bulletin, 1960/2003 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- "1981" (Box 36, Folder 18)
- S S Class Records, 1976/1979 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Flossie Clayton (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Sunday School Pictures (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Sun School, 1959/1994 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Sunday School, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Sunday School, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Souvenir Program, 1951/2003 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Mortage Burning Day Program, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Sanctuary Windows, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Dedication of Cornerstone, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Rededication of Santuary and Organ, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Rededication of Santuary, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Turner History (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Pres Johnson, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Loose Items, ca 2015 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- A New Church in the Community, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- History of Turner, 1934/1915 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- PSG Expenses, Vacs, etc (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Four Hourseman of AME Church (Box 38, Folder 7)
- I before the AME Window (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Adas Israel Turner's History, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Adas Israel to Sixth and I Historic Synagogue, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- The Church Member's Guide, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Certificate of Appreciation, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Richard Allen, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Guiles Building Dedication, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- The True Mission of Turner (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Founders Day Turner Mem, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- History of Turner, 1919 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Anniversary Submission, 1948/1949 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Turner Memorial (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Bicentennial Celebration, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Bicentennial Celebration, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- History of Turner (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Portraits in History (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Dome at Turner, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Church Window Description, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- The Train that Went to Hell (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Turner Memorial (Box 38, Folder 27)
- AME Church Time Line (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Hyattsville Church, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- History of 6 and I St, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Church Pics (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Turner MEM AMEC (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Presiding Elder Hildebrand, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Rev James Robinson (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Dr. Virginia Manning (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Board, Committees, Commissions, 1951/2002 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Health Ministry Nurses Unit, 1958/1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 4F Foundation, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- 4F Foundation, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- 4F Foundation, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Mother Bethel Program (Box 42, Folder 1)
- St George United Methodist Church Surmon, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Words of Welcome and Purpose, 2009 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Steward Board Stewardess, 1951/2002 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Loose Items, 1979/1981 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Steward's Day, 2010 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- "2002" (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Steward BD Honor Dinner, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Stewart's Honor Program, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Steward Board, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- International Usher's, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Esther Spring 100th Birthday, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Senior Usher Board (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Senior Usher Board, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Senior Usher Board, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Senior Ushers, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Senior Usher Board, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Usher Board, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Senior Usher Board (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Certificate of Appreciation, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Senior Usher Board (Box 44, Folder 11)
- 67th Annual Convention of National United Ushers, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Junior and Young People's Bd, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Junior Ushers, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Junior Ushers (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Senior Usher Board, 1952/1967 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Senior Usher Board, 1972/1990 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Ushers, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Interdenominational Ushers, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Ushers, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Ushers, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Heaven's Window, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Warren Ashe, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Adminstrative Staff (Box 46, Folder 1)
- The John Sewell Family (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Loose Items, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Guidelines for Trustees in the Local Church, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Trustee Bd Resolution, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Trustees of Turner, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Church Trustee Fellowship of Metropolitan Washington (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Church Directory (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Newspaper Item (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Mrs. Daisy Powell, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Mrs. Braxton, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Yusef Chisholm, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- General Conf, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- "2000" (Box 49, Folder 7)
- TAME Times, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Newsletter, 1992/1994 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- TAME Times, 1995/1998 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- New Article, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Communicator, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- The Jet Stream, 1959/1960 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Daily Christian Recorder, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Washington Post, 2014 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Turner AME Feature in Afro, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Highlights of Rev Guiles Tenure at Turner, 1956/1980 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Highlights of Pastorte Rev Guiles (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Guiles Funeral, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Photo: Rev S E Guiles (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Rev S Everette and Ann Guiles Photos (Box 50, Folder 5)
- unlabeled folder (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Rev Guiles Info (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Mrs Anne Guiles (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Rev S E Guiles (Box 50, Folder 9)
- plate (Box 50, Folder 10)
- The Dorcas, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Annual Missionary Convention, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Missionary Society, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- 56th Annual Convention Reid Temple, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 4)